joomladesigns.co.uk 2012-06-26

# Privacy Policy

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected at all times.

All Information collected at the http://www.joomladesigns.co.uk web site is is strictly confidential and will never be disclosed, sold, distributed or leased to any third parties.

Credit card information is NOT stored or collected at the Joomladesigns.co.uk web site.

All credit card payment transactions are securly processed by [paypal.com](http://www.paypal.com/ "Paypal") and at no time do we have access to your credit card details.

### What information do we collect

We may collect, store and use the following personal data when you visit or use the Joomladesigns.co.uk web site

  * Information about your visit to the web site and use of this web site which may include your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views.

  * Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering an account at the web site

  * Information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to the services we offer at the web site

### Cookies

Cookies are small files stored on your computer hard drive to track and identify which pages are being used when visiting the Joomla designs web site. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website and the services we offer at the web site. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website including registering an account, joining the template club downloading the Joomla templates we have developed and released or getting support via the web site for a Joomla template you have downloaded from the web site.

### Using Your Personal Data

Personal data submitted at this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website which include.

  1. Administer and management of the website.
  2. Improve your browsing experience by personalising the website.
  3. Enable your use of the services available on the website including membership registration, downloading Joomla templates and opening support tickets
  4. Send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications to keep you updated and information about the latest developments or services we offer at the Joomladesigns.co.uk web site.
  5. Send you email notifications which you have specifically requested when using the web site.
  6. Deal with enquiries you have made about or relating to the website.

### Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Credit card information is not stored or collected at the Joomladesigns.co.uk web site.

All credit card payment transactions are securly processed by paypal.com and at no time does Joomladesigns.co.uk have access to your credit card details.

### Sharing Your Information With Third Parties

All information collected and stored at the joomladesigns.co.uk web site is strictly confidential and will NOT be disclosed, sold, distributed or leased to any third parties.

### Policy Amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  Please check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy outlined at this web site please contact us
